https://www.jadranka-yachting.com/en/charter/privacy-policy

Search
HomeAbout usOur FleetPrimoštenMali LošinjPulaYacht basesPrimoštenLošinjMarina Tehnomont Veruda, PulaSailing programsBareboat charterCrewed charterGourmet sailingSailing the historical routesTeam buildingSailing SchoolPricelistSpecial offerVisitor's cornerRoutesJadranka yacht clubHow to reach us - Mali LosinjIt's good to knowAdriatic fuel stationsMarinasWeatherBrokeragePartnersBlogContact
Privacy policy
Jadranka Yachting d.o.o. understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used.
Share
Home
Charter
Privacy policy
Privacy Policy
BACKGROUND:
Jadranka Yachting d.o.o. understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who visits this website, www.jadranka-yachting.com (“Our Site”) and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy [is deemed to occur upon your first use of Our. If you do not accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Site immediately.
1. Definitions and Interpretation
In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:  “Cookie”means a small text file placed on your computer or device by Our Site when you visit certain parts of Our Site and/or when you use certain features of Our Site. Details of the Cookies used by Our Site are set out in Part 14, below; and“Cookie Law”means the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003;
2. Information About Us
Our Site is owned and operated by Jadranka Yachting d.o.o., a limited company registered in Croatia on Commercial Court in Rijeka MBS 040229833; PB 2090708.Registered address: Dražica 1, 51550 Mali Lošinj.VAT number: 83583393873.Email address: dpo@jadranka-yachting.com.Postal Address: Dražica 1, 51550 Mali Lošinj.We are a member of Jadranka d.d., Dražica 1, 51550 Mali Lošinj, Croatia
3. What Does This Policy Cover?
This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of Our Site. Our Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
4. What is Personal Data?
Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) as ‘any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier’.Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.
5. What Are My Rights?
Under the GDPR, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:a) The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Policy should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 15.b) The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 13 will tell you how to do this.c) The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by us is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.d) The right to be forgotten, i.e. the right to ask us to delete or otherwise dispose of any of your personal data that we have. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.e) The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.f) The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.g) The right to data portability. This means that, if you have provided personal data to  us directly, we are using it with your consent or for the performance of a contract, and that data is processed using automated means, you can ask us for a copy of that personal data to re-use with another service or business in many cases.h) Rights relating to automated decision-making and provide better user experience. We do not use your personal data in this way.For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact us using the details provided in Part 15.Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.
6. What Data Do We Collect?
Depending upon your use of Our Site, we may collect some or all of the following personal and non-personal data (please also see Part 14 on our use of Cookies and similar technologies and our Cookie PolicyContact information (such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number, date of birth, profession);Payment information (including payment card numbers, billing address, and bank account information);Demographic data (such as age, gender, country, and preferred language);Information related to your reservation, stay, or visit to a property (including the Jadranka Yachting d.o.o. vessels where you have stayed, date of arrival and departure, and goods and services purchased);Copies of your correspondence if you contact us;Your interests and preferences;Information related to your use and interaction with our website like IP address, location, web browser type and version, operating system, a list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on Our Site, and the site you exit to.
7. How Do You Use My Personal Data?
Under the GDPR, we must always have a lawful basis for using personal data. This may be because the data is necessary for our performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to our use of your personal data, or because it is in our legitimate business interests to use it. Your personal data will and may be used for the following purposes:Information You Give Us: We receive and store information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, including, for example, when you stay as a guest at hotels managed by us. You decide how much information to share with us in most cases, but not sharing required information may limit your ability to engage in certain activities, such as payment information required to complete your reservation. If you submit any personal information relating to another person (e.g., if you make a reservation for another individual), you represent that you are authorised by that person to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You also represent that the information you provide is accurate.Automatic Information: When you use or interact with our website and/or use any apps that we may make available on our website, we receive and store information generated by your activity and information automatically collected from your browser or mobile device. For example, like many websites, we obtain certain information when your web browser accesses our website including your IP address, browser type, operating system, mobile network data, pages viewed and access times. This information helps us to communicate with our customers and better understand them.Information from Other Sources: We may receive information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, and other third parties. This may include information from your travel agent, airline, credit card, and other partners.Age Limitations: Jadranka Yachting d.o.o. does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from our websites from any person under the age of 18. Mandarin Oriental may collect personally identifiable information from people under the age of 18 as part of the guest registration process, but always with the consent of such person’s parent or guardian.Personalising and tailoring your experience on Our SiteSupplying our products and services to you. Your personal details are required in order for us to enter into a contract with you.Personalising and tailoring our products and services for you.Communicating with you. This may include responding to emails or calls from you.Supplying you with information by email that you have opted-in to (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE link in the email footer or sending us a personal email asking us to unsubscribe you.Analysing your use of Our Site and gathering feedback to enable us to continually improve Our Site and your user experience.With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your personal data for marketing purposes, which may include contacting you by email and telephone and text message and post with information, news, and offers on our products and services. You will not be sent any unlawful marketing or spam. We will always work to fully protect your rights and comply with our obligations under the GDPR and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, and you will always have the opportunity to opt-out.Third Parties (including Google Analytisc, Google Tag Manager, Facebook Social Graph, ClickDimensions, Connecto, Hotjar, TrustYou and Zendesk, LiveIntent, SiteScout, AddThis, Adform, Facebook Connect and Facebook Facebook Custom Audience, DoubleClick, TradeDesk, MyFonts Counter, Google Dynamic Remarketing) whose content appears on Our Site may use third-party Cookies, as detailed below in Part 14. Please refer to Part 14 for more information on controlling cookies. Please note that we do not control the activities of such third parties, nor the data that they collect and use themselves, and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such third parties.If at any point you wish to query any action that we take on the basis of this or wish to request ‘human intervention’ (i.e. have someone review the action themselves, rather than relying only on the automated method), the GDPR gives you the right to do so. Please contact us to find out more using the details in Part 15.The following automated decision-making method(s) may be used:If you fill out a web form on our site, your information will be stored in our CMS and CRM system and some amount of your past browsing on our site may be available to us to determine your interests.  We may use this information to more effectively engage with you and improve our site.  However, if you use private browsing, you may provide us your information without making your past browsing activity available to us. If you do not wish for us to have your personal information, please do not fill out any of the web forms on this site.If you provide your email address and consent for email marketing, some information is collected about when/if the email was opened and what links were clicked.  This information is used to assess the engagement and success of an email campaign.]Clicking on a link in any of these emails may cause you to be personally identified on our site and may cause some part of your past browsing history on our site to be available to our personnel so we may more effectively engage with you and improve our site.  If you do not wish for this tracking to occur, you can unsubscribe from our mailings or use private browsing mode to avoid tracking.
8. How Long Will You Keep My Personal Data?
To the extent permissible by applicable law, we will retain your personal information for such period as necessary to satisfy or to fulfill the following:the purposes for which that personal information was provided,an identifiable and ongoing business need, including record keeping,a specific legal or regulatory requirement, and/ora requirement to retain records that may be relevant to any notified regulatory investigations or active legal proceedings.Where there is no sufficient justification to retain such personal information, such personal information will be safely and securely deleted, disposed of, anonymised and/or blocked.We will not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. At the time we no longer need your personal information for any business or legal purpose, we will delete it. We retain the personal information we process on behalf of our customers as long as we have an agreement with them to process that data, subject always to applicable legal requirements.
9. How and Where Do You Store or Transfer My Personal Data?
We will only store or transfer your personal data within the European Economic Area (the “EEA”). The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus UK, Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein. This means that your personal data will be fully protected under the GDPR or to equivalent standards by law.Where we transfer your data to a third party based in the US, this may be protected if they are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield. This requires that third party to provide data protection to standards similar to those in Europe. More information is available from the European Commission.Please contact us using the details below in Part 15 for further information about the particular data protection mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data to a third country.The security of your personal data is essential to us, and to protect your data, we take a number of important measures.
10. Do You Share My Personal Data?
We will not share any of your personal data with any third parties for any purposes, subject to one important exception.In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.If any personal data is transferred outside of the EEA, we will take suitable steps in order to ensure that your personal data is treated just as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the GDPR, as explained above in Part 9.In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.
11. How Can I Control My Personal Data?
1.1 In addition to your rights under the GDPR, set out in Part 5, when you submit personal data via Our Site, you may be given options to restrict our use of your personal data. In particular, we aim to give you strong controls on our use of your data for direct marketing purposes (including the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from us which you may do by unsubscribing using the links provided in our emails and, at the point of providing your details and by managing your Account).1.2 You may also wish to sign up to one or more of the preference services operating in the Croatia: The Telephone Preference Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing. Please note, however, that these services will not prevent you from receiving marketing communications that you have consented to receiving.
12. Can I Withhold Information?
You may access certain areas of Our Site without providing any personal data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on Our Site you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of certain data.You may restrict our use of Cookies. For more information, see Part 14 and our Cookie Policy.
13. How Can I Access My Personal Data?
If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a “subject access request”.All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 15. To make this as easy as possible for you, a Subject Access Request Form is available for you to use. You do not have to use this form, but it is the easiest way to tell us everything we need to know to respond to your request as quickly as possible.There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’ (for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.We will respond to your subject access request within one month of receiving it. Normally, we aim to provide a complete response, including a copy of your personal data within that time. In some cases, however, particularly if your request is more complex, more time may be required up to a maximum of three months from the date we receive your request. You will be kept fully informed of our progress.
14. How Do You Use Cookies?
[Our Site may place and access certain first-party Cookies on your computer or device. First-party Cookies are those placed directly by us and are used only by us. We use Cookies to facilitate and improve your experience of Our Site and to provide and improve our products and services. We have carefully chosen these Cookies and have taken steps to ensure that your privacy and personal data is protected and respected at all times.By using Our Site, you may also receive certain third-party Cookies on your computer or device. Third-party Cookies are those placed by websites, services, and/or parties other than us. Third-party Cookies are used on Our Site for providing a better user experience. For more details, please refer to the table below. These Cookies are not integral to the functioning of Our Site and your use and experience of Our Site will not be impaired by refusing consent to them.All Cookies used by and on Our Site are used in accordance with current Cookie Law.Before Cookies are placed on your computer or device, you will be shown a pop-up requesting your consent to set those Cookies. By giving your consent to the placing of Cookies you are enabling us to provide the best possible experience and service to you. You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of our Site may not function fully or as intended.[Certain features of Our Site depend on Cookies to function. Cookie Law deems these Cookies to be “strictly necessary”. These Cookies are shown in the table below. Your consent will not be sought to place these Cookies, but it is still important that you are aware of them. You may still block these Cookies by changing your internet browser’s settings as detailed below, but please be aware that Our Site may not work properly if you do so. We have taken great care to ensure that your privacy is not at risk by allowing them.
The following first-party Cookies may be placed on your computer or device:
Functional CookiesIf you click the button on the cookie banner, that cookie prevents showing the banner again. If using a contact form, a session cookie is set.and the following third-party Cookies may be placed on your computer or device:Google AdWordsWe may use Google AdWords to help us deliver advertising and measure the effectiveness of our campaigns. We may also use this tool to collect location information, create audience segments, and for remarketing purposes. Click here to learn more or set your preferences.Learn more: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enGoogle Dynamic RemarketingWe use these tracking tools to track user behavior over time and across third party sites to improve the effectiveness of our online advertising. We collect information about what ads users view and whether they click on the ads. We use this information to improve and customise our advertising. Click here to learn more or set your preferences.Learn more: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enGoogle Tag ManagerWe use Google Tag Manager in order to track user behavior, traffic analysis and marketing optimization. This includes manageing third party tags. Click here to learn more or set your preferences.Learn more: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enDoubleClickDoubleClick uses cookies to improve advertising. Some common applications are to target advertising based on what’s relevant to a user, to improve reporting on campaign performance and to avoid showing ads that the user has already seen.Learn more: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enFacebook Connect and Facebook Facebook Custom AudienceWe use this technology to allow users to share their experiences with our websites on Facebook and to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.To opt-out, log out of your Facebook account and visit aboutads.info/choices.ZopimWe use this cookie to understand visitor and user preferences and improve their experience, and track and analyze usage, navigational and other statistical information. If you disable cookies, you may still visit the Website and use the Services, but your ability use some features or areas of our Websites or Services may be limited.Learn more:https://www.zendesk.com/company/cookie-policy/MyFonts CounterWe use a web font from myfonts.com. Due to the license terms, a page-view tracking is performed by counting the number of visits to our website for statistical purposes and transmitting them to MyFonts.Learn more:https://www.myfonts.com/info/terms-and-conditionsTradeDeskThe Trade Desk is an online demand-side platform that provides buying tools for digital media buyers. The conversion pixel we add allows us to track performance and derive insights for media investments made.Learn more:https://thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy#optoutAdformAdform’s technology is used to create and deliver rich and diverse online marketing. They can be used for the following tasks: displaying ads in a sequence, displaying particular products in response to interest, displaying ads based on statistical probabilities, or deciding if an ad should be shown based on responses to the above techniques.Learn more: https://site.adform.com/uncategorized/product-and-services-privacy-policy/AddThisThese cookies provide user measurement and analytics features, as well as managing user sharing preferences.Learn more: http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policySiteScoutThis cookie is used to track the success of your campaign by reporting back an action that the user has completed on your website after arriving through an advertisement.Learn more: http://www.sitescout.com/privacyLiveIntentTo provide you with advertising that is as relevant and useful as possible. Some of the online ads you may see may be based on the content of the page you’re visiting, some may be based on registration information you provide, and other ads may be customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to other web sites.Learn more: https://liveintent.com/privacy-policy/
16. How Do I Contact You?
To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following details [(for the attention of:Email address: dpo@jadranka-yachting.com.Postal Address: Dražica 1, 51550 Mali Lošinj.
17. Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Discount -20%
20 Mar - 27 Mar 2021
Elan 434 impressio | Ava
Marina Tehnomont Veruda, Pula, Croatia
13.41 m
4
8 + 2
2
See Our Fleet
We use cookies to provide high quality service experience to our clients and full functionality of our website. By continuing to use our website without changing your cookie settings, you agree to our use of cookies in accordance with our Cookies Policy
Thank you for accepting cookies.
You disallowed the use of cookies.
Go Top
